Guide to the Steven H. Scheuer Collection of Television Program Scripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- ALPHABETICAL LISTING OF SCRIPTS BY PROGRAM TITLES
  - THE BIG STORY
    Writers: Gail Ingram, Ed King, Norman Lessing, Alex Leftwich, Max Ehrlich, Leonard Valenta, Alvin Boretz, Jerome Coopersmith, Mel Goldberg, Sheldon Stark, Allan Sloane, Norman Borisoff, Paul Monash, Douglas Taylor, Alan Cooke, Newton Meltzer, David Rich, and Leon Tokatyan
    - Episode #298, 1952 Oct 29 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Episode #243, 1953 Apr 17 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Episode #235, 1953 Apr 24 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Episode #236, 1953 May 1 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Episode #237, 1953 May 8 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Episode #238, 1953 May 15 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Episode #239, 1953 May 22 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Episode #242, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Episode #246, 1953 Sep 4 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Episode #248, 1953 Sep 18 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Episode #311, 1954 Jan 28 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Episode #313, 1954 Feb 11 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Episode #297, 1954 Oct 22 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Episode #301, 1954 Nov 19 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Episode #302, 1954 Nov 19 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Episode #304, 1954 Dec 10 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Episode #305, 1954 Dec 17 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Episode #306, 1954 Dec 24 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Episode #312, 1955 Feb 4 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Episode #314, 1955 Feb 18 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Episode #315, 1955 Feb 25 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Episode #316, 1955 Mar 4 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Episode #318, 1955 Mar 18 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Episode #320, 1955 Apr 1 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Episode #321, 1955 Apr 8 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Episode #322, 1955 Apr 15 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Episode #323, 1955 Apr 22 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Episode #324, 1955 Apr 29 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Episode #325, 1955 May 6 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Episode #326 (2 copies), 1955 May 13 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Episode #327, 1955 May 20 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Episode #328, 1955 May 27 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Episode #329, 1955 Jun 3 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Episode #330, 1955 Jun 10 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Episode #331, 1955 Jun 17 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Episode #332, 1955 Jun 24 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Episode #333, 1955 Jul 1 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Episode #335, 1955 Sep 9 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Episode #336, 1955 Sep 16 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Episode #337, 1955 Sep 23 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Episode #338, 1955 Sep 30 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Episode #340, 1955 Oct 14 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Episode #341, 1955 Oct 21 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Episode #343, 1955 Nov 4 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Episode #348, 1955 Dec 4 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Episode #351, 1955 Dec 30 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Episode #354, 1956 Jan 20 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Episode #355, 1956 Jan 27 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Episode #356, 1956 Feb 3 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Episode #357, 1956 Feb 10 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Episode #358, 1956 Feb 17 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Episode #361, 1956 Mar 9 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Episode #366, 1956 Apr 13 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Episode #367, 1956 Apr 20 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Episode #368, 1956 Apr 27 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Episode #369, 1956 May 4 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Episode #370, 1956 May 11 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Episode #371, 1956 May 18 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Episode #373, 1956 Jun 1 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Episode #374, 1956 Jun 8 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Episode #375, 1956 Jun 15 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Episode #376, 1956 Jun 22 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Episode #377, 1956 Jun 29 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Episode #378, 1956 Jul 6 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Episode #383, 1956 Oct 12 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Episode #383, 1956 Oct 12 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Episode #384, 1956 Oct 19 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - 1957 Jan 11 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Episode #394, 1957 Jan 18 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Episode #395, 1957 Feb 1 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Episode #396, 1957 Feb 8 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Episode #398, 1957 Mar 1 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Episode #399, 1957 Mar 8 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Episode #400, 1957 Mar 15 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Episode #401, 1957 Mar 29 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Episode #403, 1957 Apr 12 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Episode #404, 1957 Apr 26 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - fragment (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - BIOGRAPHY
    Biographical sketches, hosted by Mike Wallace.
    (no dates indicated, but all scripts apparently from 1964)
    - Theodore Roosevelt (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Will Rogers (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Mao-Tse-Tung (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Truman (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Charles DeGaulle (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - BOB AND RAY
    Short comedy skits
    (no year indicated)
    - n.y. May 4 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - n.y. May 25 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - THE BOB CROSBY SHOW
    Producers: Gil Rodin
    Directors: Jack Orbison, Herb Allen, Phil Callahan, Ben Feiner, Greg Garrison, Louis Da Pron, Cort Steen
    Writers: Carroll Carroll, Jack Lloyd, Mort Greene, Seaman Jacobs, Hank Grant, Hal Finsberg, Tom Waldman, Hugh Wedlock, and Howard Snyder
    (dates indicated appear to be script dates, not air dates)
    - 1954 Aug 30 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - 1954 Aug 31 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - 1954 Sep 1 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - 1954 Sep 2 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - 1954 Sep 3 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - 1954 Sep 7 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - 1954 Sep 8 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - 1954 Sep 9 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - 1954 Sep 28 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - 1954 Sep 29 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - 1954 Sep 30 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - 1954 Oct 1 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - 1954 Nov 23 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - 1955 Jan 25 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - 1955 Feb 1 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - 1955 Feb 7 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - 1955 Feb 8 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - 1955 Mar 15 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - 1955 May 31 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - 1955 Jul 25 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - 1955 Aug 12 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - 1955 Aug 15 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - 1955 Aug 16 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - 1955 Aug 17 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - 1955 Aug 19 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - 1955 Aug 22 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - 1955 Aug 23 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - 1955 Aug 24 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - 1955 Aug 25 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - 1955 Aug 26 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - 1955 Aug 29 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - 1955 Aug 30 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Episode #3, 1958 Jun 28 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Episode #4, 1958 Jul 5 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Episode #5, 1958 Jul 12 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Episode #6, 1958 Jul 19 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Episode #7, 1958 Jul 26 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Episode #8, 1958 Aug 2 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Episode #9, 1958 Aug 9 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Episode #10, 1958 Aug 16 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Episode #12, 1958 Aug 30 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - BONINO
    Situation Comedy
    Producer: Fred Coe
    Writers: Robert Alan Aurthur and David Shaw
    - Episode #3, 1953 Sep 26 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Episode #4, 1953 Oct 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Episode #5, 1953 Oct 10 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Episode #6, 1953 Oct 17 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Episode #7, 1953 Oct 24 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Episode #8, 1953 Oct 31 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Episode #9, 1953 Nov 7 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Episode #10, 1953 Nov 14 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Episode #11, 1953 Nov 21 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Episode #12, 1953 Nov 28 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Episode #13, 1953 Dec 5 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Episode #14, 1953 Dec 12 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Episode #16, 1953 Dec 26 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - BREAKTHROUGH
    Medical Documentary
    Producer: Lou Hazam
    Director: Charles Christensen
    Writer: Leonard Engel
    - Cancer Virus, 1962 Mar (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Mental Illness, 1962 Jun 22 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - BRECK SUNDAY SHOWCASE
    Music, variety, with Boris Karloff
    - 1960 Apr 3 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - BRILLO STAR TONIGHT
    See: "Star Tonight"
  - CAESAR PRESENTS
    Comedy, variety. Summer name of "Caesar's Hour."
    Producer: George Charles
    Directors: Grey Lockwood and Carl Reiner
    Writers: Selma Diamond, Shelly Keller, Lou Solomon, and Mike Stewart
    - Episode #2, 1955 Jul 11 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Episode #7, 1955 Aug 25 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - CAESAR'S HOUR
    Comedy, variety. (In 1958 name changed to "Sid Caesar Invites You")
    See also previous listing
    Producers: Leo Morgan
    Directors: Clark Jones, Hal Janis, Frank Bunetta
    Writers: Mel Brooks, Larry Gelbart, Mel Tolkin, Mike Stewart, Shelly Keller, Selma Diamond, and Gary Belkin
    - Episode #18, 1955 Feb 28 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Episode #31, 1955 Sep 26 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Episode #33, 1955 Oct 10 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Episode #34, 1955 Oct 24 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Episode #35, 1955 Oct 31 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Episode #36, 1955 Nov 7 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Episode #38, 1955 Nov 28 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Episode #40, 1955 Dec 19 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Episode #43, 1956 Jan 16 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Episode #50, 1956 Mar 19 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Episode #53, 1956 Apr 16 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Episode #54, 1956 Apr 23 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Episode #55, 1956 May 7 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Episode #56, 1956 May 14 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Episode #57, 1956 May 21 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Episode #58, 1956 Jun 4 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Episode #59, 1956 Jun 11 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Episode #62, 1956 Sep 22 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Episode #63, 1956 Oct 6 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Episode #64, 1956 Oct 13 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Episode #65, 1956 Oct 20 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Episode #70, 1956 Dec 8 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Episode #71, 1956 Dec 15 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Episode #73, 1957 Jan 5 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Episode #75, 1957 Jan 26 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Episode #76, 1957 Feb 2 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Episode #77, 1957 Feb 9 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Episode #78, 1957 Feb (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Episode #79, 1957 Mar 2 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Episode #80, 1957 Mar 9 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Episode #82, 1957 Mar 30 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Episode #83, 1957 Apr 6 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Episode #84, 1957 Apr 20 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Episode #85, 1957 Apr 27 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Episode #86, 1957 May 4 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Episode #87, 1957 May 18 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Episode #4, 1958 Feb 16 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Episode #5, 1958 Feb 23 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Episode #10, 1958 Mar 30 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Episode #11, 1958 Apr 6 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Episode #14, 1958 Apr 27 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Episode #17, 1958 May 18 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Episode #18, 1958 May 25 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Fragments nos 39 and 69 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - CALENDAR
    "Informational variety," with Harry Reasoner
    - Episode #2, 1962 July 12 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - CAMEO THEATER
    TV Drama
    Director: Albert McCleery
    - The Man from the South Peter Kortner, 1955 Aug 14 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - CAMERA THREE
    Art, music, and literature. Documentary and dramatizations.
    Producers: Robert Herridge
    Directors: Francis Moriarty, John McGiffert, John Desmond, Clair Roskam, Nick Havinga, Max Miller, and Anthony Farrar
    Writers: Clair Roskam, Joseph Hurley, Sig Moglen, (Most of the scripts are not actually complete. Apparently they do not include the opening or closing, and often the dialogue is not transcribed.)
    - Impressionists, 1956 Apr 22 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Elizabethan Miscellany I, 1956 Apr 29 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Elizabethan Miscellany I, 1956 May 6 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Elizabethan Miscellany III, 1956 May 13 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Nonsense (Edward Lear), 1956 Jun 10 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Stanislavsky and the Art of Acting, 1956 Jul 22 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Jazz, 1956 Jul 29 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Daisy Miller, 1956 Aug 5 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - American Travelers, 1956 Aug 12 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Modern Dance, 1956 Aug 19 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - As I Lay Dying, 1956 Oct 7 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Frederic The Great & Catherine the Great, 1957 Feb 10 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Individuality and Standardization, 1957 Mar 3 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - L'Histoire du Soldat, 1957 Mar 10 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - The Brownstone Ages (Edith Wharton), 1957 Mar 24 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Anton Chekhov, Frank O'Connor, 1957 Apr 28 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - The American Presidency, 1957 May 19 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - The Idiot (Dostoevsky), 1957 Dec 22 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Letters of Katherine Mansfield, Napoleon, Abelard, 1958 Feb 9 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - W. H. Auden, 1958 Mar 2 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Krazy Kat, 1958 Mar 16 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Science fantasy - A trip to the moon, 1958 Mar 23 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Philoctetes, 1958 Mar 30 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Sacco and Vanzetti, part I, 1958 May 4 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - The Antagonists--Lee, 1958 May 18 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - The Antagonists--Grant, 1958 May 24 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - London by Dickens, 1958 Jun 1 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Poet in New York--Lorca, 1958 Jun 15 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Joyce and Donleavy, 1958 Jul 20 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Yeats, 1958 Jul 27 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Ivy Day in the Committee Room, 1958 Aug 17 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Ad Astra, 1958 Sep 7 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Faulkner--"The Tall Men", 1958 Sep 15 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Thurber, 1958 Oct 12 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Lorenzo da Ponte, 1958 Nov 2 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Captain Stormfield's Visit to Heaven (Twain), 1958 Nov 9 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Rene Clair, 1958 Nov 16 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - 7 Wonders of American Architecture, 1958 Nov 23 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Pere Goriot, 1958 Dec 14 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Poetry - Frost, Dickenson, etc., 1958 Dec 21 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Solitude, 1958 Dec 28 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Sam Chamberlain, 1959 Jan 4 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Shoshana Damari, 1959 Jan 11 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Fathers, 1959 Jan 18 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Jazz Dance, 1959 Jan 25 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - The Last Days of Lincoln (Mark Van Doren), 1959 Feb 8 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Ship of Fools (Katherine Ann Porter), 1959 Feb 22 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Man with a Mouth Organ--Larry Adler, 1959 Mar 8 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Angna Enters, 1959 Mar 15 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - An Air that Kills (Housman), 1959 Mar 22 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Bartleby (Melville), 1959 Apr 5 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Sarah Orne Jewett, 1959 Apr 12 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - The Sting of Satire, part I, 1959 Apr 19 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - The Sting of Satire, part II, 1959 Apr 26 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - The Artist as Illustrator (Marc Simont), 1959 May 3 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Whistler's Father, 1959 May 10 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Madame Recamier, 1959 May 17 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - E. M. Forster, 1959 May 24 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Actor's Choice: Dorothy Stickney, 1959 May 31 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - The Pleasures of Purcell, 1959 Jun 7 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Actor's Choice #2: Mory Perry, 1959 Jun 21 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Lost Hearts, 1959 Jun 28 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Morton Gould - composing, 1959 Jul 12 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Harold Clurman - acting, 1959 Jul 19 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - The Eagle, The Tiger, The Fly, 1959 Jul 26 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Ambrose Bierce, 1959 Aug 2 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - The Film: Realism and Fantasy, 1959 Aug 30 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Knights and Ladies, 1959 Sep 6 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Ballads, 1959 Sep 13 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - At the End of the Passage, 1959 Sep 20 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - The Stout Gentleman, 1959 Sep 27 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Controlled Chance: Non-Jazz Improvisation, 1959 Oct 11 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Selma Broter, 1959 Oct 25 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Eudora Welty, 1959 Nov 1 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Eskimos, 1959 Nov 8 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Poverty, 1959 Nov 15 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - The Humor Hardy, 1959 Nov 27 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Winter Words (Hardy), 1959 Nov 29 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - From Hiroshima to the Moon, 1959 Dec 20 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Actor's Choice #3: Maureen Stapleton, 1960 Jan 10 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Benjamin Franklin, 1960 Jan 17 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Katherine Ann Porter and Cotton Mather, 1960 Jan 24 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Il Filosofo di Compagna, 1960 Feb 7 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - The Way of All Flesh, 1960 Feb 28 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Sicily, 1960 Mar 27 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Harriet Tubman, 1960 Apr 3 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Chitra, 1960 Apr 8 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - The Destroyer (Elizabeth Bowen), 1960 May 15 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Boswell without Johnson, 1960 May 29 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Shari Ophir - mime, 1960 Jun 5 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Political exiles, 1960 Jun 12 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - What to do with Ex-Presidents, 1960 Jul 3 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Ten Men from Company K, 1960 Jul 17 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Rationalizing, 1960 Jul 24 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - A Night With Chichikov (Gogol), 1960 Aug 21 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Jane Austen's Matchmaker, 1960 Aug 28 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Acting, 1960 Sep 4 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Culture Shock (Americans Abroad), 1960 Sep 18 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Knowing One Another (Americans Abroad), 1960 Sep 25 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - On a Strange Shore (Hudson), 1960 Oct 9 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - In Tilbury Town (E. A. Robinson), 1960 Oct 23 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Songs of William Blake, 1960 Nov 6 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Actor's Choice #7: Rubie Dee and Ossie Davis, 1960 Nov 13 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - A Former Security Risk, 1960 Dec 11 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Mark Tapley (Martin Chuzzlewit), 1961 Jan 8 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Food & Drink, 1961 Jan 15 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - The Playground (John Hersey), 1961 Jan 22 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - The Essential Scott (Robert Burns), 1961 Jan 29 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Through Foreign Eyes (Lincoln), 1961 Feb 12 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Self-Pity, 1961 Feb 19 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Africanization, 1961 Mar 5 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Three Stories by Katherine Mansfield, 1961 Apr 9 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Sarah Orne Jewett, 1961 Apr 23 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Peter Goldthwaite's Treasure (Hawthorne), 1961 Apr 30 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - The Accused, 1961 May 7 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - The Whims of Genius (music), 1961 May 17 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - The Cracked Lookinglass, 1961 May 28 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Don Juan, 1961 Jun 18 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Peter Altenberg, 1961 Jun 25 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - The Chance to Grow (Summerhill), 1961 Jul 16 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Nina Simone, 1961 Aug 13 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Songs of the Hebrides, 1961 Sep 10 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Morning Colors: Music of India, 1961 Sep 24 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - A Simple Heart (Flaubert), 1961 Oct 1 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - The Legal Process of Anton Chekhov, 1961 Oct 29 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - The Butterfly Dream (Drama of China), 1961 Nov 12 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Rosalyn Tureck (Bach), 1961 Dec 17 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - A Child's Christmas in Wales (read by Richard Burton), 1961 Dec 24 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - The Art of Julian Bream (lute), 1962 Mar 4 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Robinson Jeffers, 1962 Mar 18 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - The Comic Barr: Fernando Corena, 1962 Apr 15 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Stalingrad, World War II, 1962 Apr 29 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - An Introduction to Bach performance (Tureck), 1962 Oct 7 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - The Jazz of Bill Evans, 1962 Oct 21 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Parnassus '63, 1963 Jan 20 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Max Frisch, 1963 Mar 3 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - The Diaries of Wanda Landowska, with Agnes Moorehead, 1963 Mar 17 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - John Weaver, 1963 Mar 24 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Pllack Plays Chopin, 1963 Jul 14 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - A Tribute to Lester Horton, 1963 Jul 28 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Henry David Thoreau, 1963 Aug 11 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Eudora Welty, 1963 Aug 18 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Women, 1963 Sep 11 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Folksongs, with Martha Schlamme & Will Holt, 1963 Oct 13 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Tribute to Ted (Roethke), 1963 Oct 27 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Letters of Robert Frost to Louis Untermeyer, 1963 Nov 3 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - William Carlos Williams, 1963 Nov 10 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - The Face of War, 1963 Nov 17 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Ruth Slenczynska, 1963 Nov 24 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Christmas, 1963 Dec 22 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Opera Buffs, 1964 Jan 26 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Notes from Underground (3 parts), undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - The Image of Walt Whitman, undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Rime of the Ancient Mariner, undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Crito Visits Socrates in Prison, undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Letters from the Earth (Twain), undated (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - John Keats, undated (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - The Poorhouse Fair (John Updike), undated (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Fathers and Sons (Turgenev), undated (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - W. H. Auden Interview, undated (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Republican Convention (Truman), undated (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Song without Words, undated (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Enemies (Chekhov), undated (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Conversations from "Catch 22", undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Dialogues in Dance, undated (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - (no title), undated (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - (no title), undated (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - CAMPBELL SOUNDSTAGE
    TV Drama, NBC
    Producer: Martin Horrell
    Director: Garry Simpson
    - Reveille For Two Angels #23 S. Lee Pogostin, 1953 Jan 1 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Innocent, 'til Proved Guilty Frank P. DeFelitta, 1953 Jul 10 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Run Away Jesse Sandler, 1953 Aug 7 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Deception #6 Jesse Sandler, 1953 Aug 14 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Episode #7, 1953 Aug 21 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - THE DARK ROOM
    Ellis St. Joseph
    - Wonder in Your Eyes #8 S. Lee Pogostin, 1953 Aug 28 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - The Square Hole Frank P. DeFelitta, 1953 Sep 4 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Exit Laughing #11 Jesse Sandler, 1953 Sep 18 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - The Last Spring #13 Jesse Sandler, 1953 Oct 2 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Darling, Come Home #14 Frank P. DeFelitta, 1953 Oct 9 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Life Sentence #15 S. Lee Pogostin, 1953 Oct 16 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Johnny No-name #16 Jesse Sandler, 1953 Oct 23 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Nemesis #17 S. Lee Pogostin, 1953 Oct 30 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - The Meaning of Truth #18 Jesse Sandler, 1953 Nov 6 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Ten Little Words #19 Jesse Sandler, 1953 Nov 13 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Solitaire #20 Frank P. DeFelitta, 1953 Nov 20 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Too Little a Kiss #23 Frank P. DeFelitta, 1953 Dec 11 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - The Man Who Knew O. Henry #24 Jesse Sandler, 1953 Dec 18 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - The Happy Headline #25 Jesse Sandler (original by Rod Serling), 1953 Dec 25 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Marked Money Jesse Sandler, 1954 Jan 8 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - The Golden Box #32 Jesse Sandler, 1954 Feb 12 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Journey to Java #33 Frank P. DeFelitta, 1954 Feb 19 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - God's Children James Truex, 1954 Apr 2 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - XXXXX Isn't Everything Max Wilk, 1954 Apr 9 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - The Almighty Dollar Greer Johnson, 1954 Apr 23 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Al Toolum and his Buddy Leo Robert Alan Aurthur, 1954 Apr 30 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Emma's Antenna Hamilton Benz, 1954 May 7 (Box 58, Folder 10)